George M. Gray Museum Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Original Labels, Series II
  - Gray Museum Labels. These are archived Gray Museum labels removed from specimens., 1960-1994; 001959
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 928., 1960-1994; 006458
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 3284., 1960-1994; 006459
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 817., 1960-1994; 006460
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7426., 1960-1994; 006461
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7425., 1960-1994; 006462
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 1217., 1960-1994; 006463
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 927., 1960-1994; 006464
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 986., 1960-1994; 006465
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 3989., 1960-1994; 006466
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 926., 1960-1994; 006467
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 925., 1960-1994; 006468
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 941., 1960-1994; 006469
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7418., 1960-1994; 006470
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 2740., 1960-1994; 006471
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 134., 1960-1994; 006472
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 937., 1960-1994; 006473
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 943., 1960-1994; 006474
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 7429., 1960-1994; 006475
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 947., 1960-1994; 006476
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 945., 1960-1994; 006477
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 960., 1960-1994; 006478
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 1176., 1960-1994; 006479
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original label for GM 764., 1960-1994; 006480
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7038., 1960-1994; 006481
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 1326., 1960-1994; 006482
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 707., 1960-1994; 006483
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7036., 1960-1994; 006484
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7592., 1960-1994; 006485
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 242., 1960-1994; 006486
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 658., 1960-1994; 006487
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 423., 1960-1994; 006488
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 4785., 1960-1994; 006489
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7259., 1960-1994; 006490
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7577., 1960-1994; 006491
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7381., 1960-1994; 006492
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7579., 1960-1994; 006493
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 638., 1960-1994; 006494
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 1326., 1960-1994; 006495
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 539., 1960-1994; 006496
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 629., 1960-1994; 006497
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 3491., 1960-1994; 006498
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 2262., 1960-1994; 006499
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 6500., 1960-1994; 006500
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original determination label for YPM No. 81988 - 82090. R.H.Parker, Hadley Harbor Series of Phoxocephalus holbolli., 1960-1994; 006501
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 1010., 1960-1994; 006502
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 981., 1960-1994; 006503
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 6240., 1960-1994; 006504
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 6282., 1960-1994; 006505
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 1219., 1960-1994; 006506
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 801., 1960-1994; 006507
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 4609., 1960-1994; 006508
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 82., 1960-1994; 006509
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 3945., 1960-1994; 006510
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 7583., 1960-1994; 006511
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 1993., 1960-1994; 006512
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 2253., 1960-1994; 006513
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for GM 3799., 1960-1994; 006514
    - Gray Museum Labels. Original labels for slides of Hoploplana inquilina (c 968 series)., 1960-1994; 006525
- Catalog Sheets, Series III
  - GM 1301-1400., 002695
    - GM 1329., 002696
    - GM 7010. GM 7010 was used twice. See attached sheets., 002806
- Systematic Ecology Program, Series IV
  - Systematic Ecology Program Collecting Sites. Card file of SEP collecting sites., 005632
    - SEP0001. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1-99., 005633
    - SEP0100. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 100-199., 005634
    - SEP0200. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 200-299., 005635
    - SEP0300. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 300-399., 005636
    - SEP0400. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 400-499., 005637
    - SEP0500. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 500-599., 005638
    - SEP0600. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 600-699., 005639
    - SEP0700. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 700-799., 005640
    - SEP0800. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 800-899., 005641
    - SEP0900. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 900-999., 005642
    - SEP1000. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1000-1099., 005643
    - SEP1100. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1100-1199., 005644
    - SEP1200. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1200-1299., 005645
    - SEP1300. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1300-1399., 005646
    - SEP1400. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1400-1499., 005647
    - SEP1500. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1500-1599., 005648
    - SEP1600. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1600-1699., 005649
    - SEP1700. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1700-1799., 005650
    - SEP1800. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1800-1899., 005651
    - SEP1900. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 1900-1999., 005652
    - SEP2000. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 2000-2099., 005653
    - SEP2100. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 2100-2424., 005654
    - SEP3136. Systematic Ecology Program collecting sites 3136-3149., 005655